[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1",
        "question": "Helping Hands Club had 57 sandwiches. They served 33 sandwiches. How many sandwiches are left?",
        "options": [
            "24",
            "22",
            "25",
            "23"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2",
        "question": "Ruby had 49 apples. She served 28 apples. How many apples are left?",
        "options": [
            "23",
            "25",
            "21",
            "22"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3",
        "question": "The club had 53 juice boxes. They used 30 juice boxes. How many juice boxes are left?",
        "options": [
            "25",
            "23",
            "21",
            "24"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4",
        "question": "Ruby’s Helping Hands Club had 66 cookies. They served 46 cookies. How many cookies are left?",
        "options": [
            "17",
            "19",
            "18",
            "20"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5",
        "question": "Ruby had 34 bags of chips. She used 23 bags. How many bags of chips are left?",
        "options": [
            "11",
            "13",
            "12",
            "14"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6",
        "question": "Ruby’s Helping Hands Club collected 58 bananas. They served 45 bananas. How many bananas are left?",
        "options": [
            "12",
            "11",
            "13",
            "14"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7",
        "question": "The club had 66 water bottles. They used 45 water bottles. How many water bottles are left?",
        "options": [
            "19",
            "22",
            "23",
            "21"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8",
        "question": "Ruby had 59 pies. She served 24 pies. How many pies are left?",
        "options": [
            "35",
            "34",
            "36",
            "31"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9",
        "question": "They had 65 bread rolls. They served 53 bread rolls. How many bread rolls are left?",
        "options": [
            "13",
            "12",
            "11",
            "14"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10",
        "question": "The club had 74 dessert bars. They served 32 dessert bars. How many dessert bars are left?",
        "options": [
            "43",
            "45",
            "42",
            "41"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    }
]